Back inside our component,
回到我们的内部
we're gonna add a list of the people who are attending our event.
我们要增加一个变量来记录出席我们活动的人数
Here in the setup method,
在setup方法里面
we're gonna add in the attending array,
我们增加了一个attending这样的一个变量的数组
which is a reactive reference.
这是响应式的ref属性
We'll give our template access to it.
在template中是可以直接访问到它的
And then we'll print the list of those who are attending.
然后我们输出出席的人的名字
Our component now looks something like this.
组件在浏览器中式这样显示的
In addition to printing our capacity,
除了在template打印capacity
we now want to show our users how many spaces are left in our event.
现在，我们希望向用户显示在活动中还留有多少位置
so In order to calculate this, using our regular components in Synatx, we might create a computer property,
为了计算spaceLeft，使用Vue2.0的常规语法，我们可以写一个computed属性
which takes the current capacity subtracted by
它将当前capacity减去
the length of our attending array.
attending的数组的长度
How might we do this using the composition? Api syntax?
我们如何使用composition API 来实现这个功能?
I'll shorten our template to make some room.
我把模板缩短，腾出一些空间。
And now inside of our set up method,
现在在setup方法中，
first,
首先，
we need to import the computed function.
我们需要导入计算函数。
Then
然后
will create a new constant called spacesLeft,
将创建一个名为spacesLeft的新量
which sends into the computed function an anonymous function,
spaceLefts将匿名函数派发到计算函数中，
which returns the result of taking capacity and subtracting the number of people who are attending.
它返回的结果是capacity减去attending的length的结果
Notice I have to use dot value here.
注意，这里我必须使用.value
Since I'm dealing with two reactive references,
因为我要处理两个响应式的Ref
I'll then give the template access to this computer property.
然后，我将给template访问这个计算机属性的权限。
I jump in the browser.
我跳到了浏览器。
I can see that everything is working
我看得出一切都在运转
with my computed property, like I'd expect.
计算属性的使用的方式跟我预期的是一样的。